[
  {
    "Question": "What is the output of the following code? console.log(2 + 2);",
    "Answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What keyword is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
    "Answer": "var"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the result of the expression \"5\" + 2?",
    "Answer": "52"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can you convert a string to an integer in JavaScript?",
    "Answer": "parseInt()"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the correct syntax to add an event listener in JavaScript?",
    "Answer": "element.addEventListener(event, function)"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the purpose of the \"this\" keyword in JavaScript?",
    "Answer": "It refers to the current object or context"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the result of the expression true && false?",
    "Answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which method is used to remove the last element from an array?",
    "Answer": "pop()"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the value of NaN in JavaScript?",
    "Answer": "Not a Number"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can you check the type of a variable in JavaScript?",
    "Answer": "typeof operator"
  }
]
